<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>crack IELTS on Darsh Khatri</title>
    <link>https://darshkhatri.com/tags/crack-ielts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in crack IELTS on Darsh Khatri</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2008–2018, Steve Francia and the Hugo Authors; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 May 2021 13:00:44 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://darshkhatri.com/tags/crack-ielts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>5 Tips for How to Crack Ielts in 10 Days</title>
      <link>https://darshkhatri.com/post/ielts/5-tips-for-how-to-crack-ielts-in-10-days/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 May 2021 13:00:44 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://darshkhatri.com/post/ielts/5-tips-for-how-to-crack-ielts-in-10-days/</guid>
      <description>
        
          &lt;p&gt;Everyone has a Dream about a study or settle in abroad. First of all, you need to learn that particular language of that country and clear exam then after you can go there. Mainly IELTS(Internation English Language Testing System) exam is best for settle or study in a foreign country.
Two bodies conduct IELT exam&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;British Academy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;IDP Academy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;you can select any.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;IELTS contains 4 modules as an examination&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Listening&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reading&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Writing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Speaking&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The first 3 modules of the exam conduct on the same day and the Speaking Exam conduct on other days.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let me brief you on how you can crack IELTS in a 10 day&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You need to be strong in &amp;quot;English Grammar&amp;quot; For this there are several books and youtube videos
available so you can study that. You must be spent 1:30 hour daily on Grammar for up to 10 days.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Watch Online WebSeries in English and listen to English songs with lyrics so you got an idea about
pronunciation as well as sentence structure. You must be spent at least 2 hours on an English web series or movie and 1 hour on English songs for up to 10 days.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You must have read at least 2 hours a day. Either English newspaper or reading a book.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Speaking is tough and you need to be required so much practice so keep pratice with friends and family 
members or practice in front of a mirror. Recording that pratice section and listen carefully and identify your mistake and correct it. You need to practice at least 2 hours a day for speaking.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You need to complete all Cambridge tests in 10 days and all test scores must be 8 bands so, you can
get 8 bands in the actual exam.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Last but not least, you need to practice as one of the best quotes I read &amp;quot;Practise makes a man perfect&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;

        
      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
