<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>yogateacher on Darsh Khatri</title>
    <link>https://darshkhatri.com/tags/yogateacher/</link>
    <description>Recent content in yogateacher on Darsh Khatri</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2008–2018, Steve Francia and the Hugo Authors; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 May 2021 16:29:40 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://darshkhatri.com/tags/yogateacher/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to Why You Need to Do Yoga Daily ?</title>
      <link>https://darshkhatri.com/post/health/weight-lose/how-to-why-you-need-to-do-yoga-daily/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2021 16:29:40 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://darshkhatri.com/post/health/weight-lose/how-to-why-you-need-to-do-yoga-daily/</guid>
      <description>
        
          &lt;h2 id=&#34;yoga-came-from-the-sanskrit-word-yug-which-means-union&#34;&gt;YOGA came from the Sanskrit word &amp;quot;YUG&amp;quot; which means &amp;quot;UNION&amp;quot;.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are countless advantages of doing yoga every day.
Today I am discussing when, why, how you should do yoga.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In today&#39;s era, no one has abundant time to maintain health due to hectic work schedules and family responsibilities. There are several ways to take your body, mind, and soul to make it healthy but one of the best ways is &lt;code&gt;YOGA&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;1-what-is-yoga&#34;&gt;1. What is yoga?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There has no perfect definition of yoga. some people point it to be &lt;code&gt;Science&lt;/code&gt; or &lt;code&gt;Meditation&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In today&#39;s digital era people are mostly not have time to do exercise but yoga helps to reduce the stress of work and maintain balance peace of mind.
A number of research proven that by doing yoga you can solve the &#39;N&#39; number of diseases. Even you can be fit and look young and energetic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;2-how-we-can-do-yoga&#34;&gt;2. How we can do yoga?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are various methods of &#39;YOGA&#39; that you need to perform without disturbance. 
There are a few methods as I illustrated via picture.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://static6.depositphotos.com/1000419/605/v/600/depositphotos_6059748-stock-illustration-woman-practicing-yoga-25-poses.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;3-when-you-need-to-do-yoga&#34;&gt;3. When you need to do yoga?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Everyone is confused when we need to do yoga? what is the best time to do yoga?
As such, there has no fixed time to do yoga but there are numerous research proven that if someone does yoga in the morning so, it is beneficial for health, body, mind, and soul.
Because in the morning person have plenty of energy that&#39;s why it is fruitful to do yoga in the morning.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;4-advantages-of-yoga&#34;&gt;4. Advantages of yoga?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are countless benefits of doing yoga on a daily but I mention a few of them below.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;h6 id=&#34;improve-heart-health&#34;&gt;Improve heart health.&lt;/h6&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If someone doing yoga daily basis so it increases blood circulation and it can help lower blood, cholesterol, blood glucose level and maintain heart rate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;h6 id=&#34;relief-back-pain&#34;&gt;Relief back pain.&lt;/h6&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are several poses in yoga that relieve you from back pain and give you the energy to maintain your daily activity fastly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;h6 id=&#34;provide-you-more-energy-and-a-healthy-heart&#34;&gt;Provide you more energy and a healthy heart.&lt;/h6&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It provides you with more energy to achieve your daily goals as well as keep you mentally and physically active.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;h6 id=&#34;quality-sleep&#34;&gt;Quality sleep.&lt;/h6&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Doing yoga every day provides you to maintain a schedule and a relaxed mind that can help you for quality sleep.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;h6 id=&#34;protects-your-spine&#34;&gt;Protects your spine.&lt;/h6&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are different types of poses in yoga so, while performing that your body will be in good shape and make your bone stronger and protect your spine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;h6 id=&#34;improve-focus-power&#34;&gt;Improve focus power.&lt;/h6&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yoga has several poses that help with meditation. With the help of that meditation focus and decision power increase so, with less time achieve more things.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;note&#34;&gt;Note:&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If you are doing yoga the first time so, you need a trainer to understand how can perform yoga otherwise it&#39;s an effective wrong way.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;mark&gt;Conclusion:&lt;/mark&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Yoga has no specific definition.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;There are several poses that you can do yoga.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Yoga has numerous benefits.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You can do yoga either morning or evening but as per professional teacher morning yoga is more  effective.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

        
      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
