<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>yogapractice on Darsh Khatri</title>
    <link>https://darshkhatri.com/tags/yogapractice/</link>
    <description>Recent content in yogapractice on Darsh Khatri</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2008–2018, Steve Francia and the Hugo Authors; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 May 2021 16:14:15 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://darshkhatri.com/tags/yogapractice/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The 5 Best Things About How to Boost Immune System Naturally</title>
      <link>https://darshkhatri.com/post/health/weight-lose/the-5-best-things-about-how-to-boost-immune-system-naturally/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 May 2021 16:14:15 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://darshkhatri.com/post/health/weight-lose/the-5-best-things-about-how-to-boost-immune-system-naturally/</guid>
      <description>
        
          &lt;p&gt;Due to &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.who.int/health-topics/coronavirus#tab=tab_1&#34;&gt;Covid-19 or Coronavirus&lt;/a&gt; was declared as a pandemic by the WHO. There are numerous people unable to fight this virus due to a lack of immunity system but today I am going to discuss some interesting things that added value to your life in this pandemic situation that cause anyone can fight against this virus.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The &lt;abbr title=&#34;World Health Organization&#34;&gt;WHO&lt;/abbr&gt;  already declared two ways to fight against this Covid-19 situation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Social distance and Wear a mask.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;frequently washing hands.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Of course, several countries found vaccines but we also need to take care individually of our immune system. now our question is How Can We improve our immune system?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;heres-the-top-5-way-to-boost-your-immune-system&#34;&gt;Here&#39;s the top 5 way to boost your immune system.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;1-quality-sleep-&#34;&gt;1. Quality Sleep :&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Immunity and sleep are closely bindings with each other. If any person is not able to get quality sleep so that links to sickness and problems. As per the doctor&#39;s suggestion any human being required a minimum 8-hour sleep. &amp;quot;Early to bed and early to rise, makes a man healthy, wealthy, and wise&amp;quot; so that slogan was given by our accident and it truly defines our lifestyle. if you are not able to sleep at a time so you need to follow the below ideas.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It is advisable to read a book before sleep so, that helps to reduce your stress and sleep deeply.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Listen to good music before sleep.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Chanting with meditation so that helps you for better sleep.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Make sure every day you are going to sleep at the same time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1603804449778-de9ddafbb4ab?ixlib=rb-1.2.1&amp;amp;ixid=MnwxMjA3fDB8MHxwaG90by1wYWdlfHx8fGVufDB8fHx8&amp;amp;auto=format&amp;amp;fit=crop&amp;amp;w=967&amp;amp;q=80&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;2-maintain-weight-&#34;&gt;2. Maintain Weight :&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the current pandemic situation, we need to take care of our body weight because it causes other issues for our body if we are overweighted. Reduce stress levels and get enough up sleep as well as exercise and meditation will help reduce weight.
if you want to know about how to reduce weight so, please read  &lt;a href=&#34;https://darshkhatri.com/post/health/weight-lose/best-2-way-to-loss-your-weight-tips/&#34;&gt;Best 2 Way to Loss Your Weight Tips.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1522844990619-4951c40f7eda?ixid=MnwxMjA3fDB8MHxwaG90by1wYWdlfHx8fGVufDB8fHx8&amp;amp;ixlib=rb-1.2.1&amp;amp;auto=format&amp;amp;fit=crop&amp;amp;w=1350&amp;amp;q=80&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;3-balance-diet--drink-water-frequantly-&#34;&gt;3. Balance Diet / Drink Water frequantly :&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Diet is a serious factor for our body and immunity. There are several ways to increase our immune system with a healthy diet. we can eat proper food that contains vitamins and properties so, it helps to improve our immune system and time is also a key factor that we can eat food at a particular time. Like before 12 pm in the morning and before 8 pm.
The human body required a minimum of 3 Liters of water. Our water consumption level also equal to or more so, which can be helpful for our body to maintain weight.
Only drink lukewarm water and avoid cold water.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1498837167922-ddd27525d352?ixid=MnwxMjA3fDB8MHxwaG90by1wYWdlfHx8fGVufDB8fHx8&amp;amp;ixlib=rb-1.2.1&amp;amp;auto=format&amp;amp;fit=crop&amp;amp;w=1350&amp;amp;q=80&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;4-excercise--meditation--yoga-&#34;&gt;4. Excercise / Meditation / Yoga :&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A lot of things depend on our daily schedule and exercise, meditation and yoga is the best part to do by a human for maintaining the body as well as improve our body system. As per professionals, we required a minimum of 30 minutes of exercise daily or meditation, yoga.
best time for excercise, meditation and yoga is in the morning and evening.
If want to know more about yoga  so visit &lt;a href=&#34;https://darshkhatri.com/post/health/weight-lose/how-to-why-you-need-to-do-yoga-daily/&#34;&gt;Why you need to do yoga daily?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1487956382158-bb926046304a?ixlib=rb-1.2.1&amp;amp;ixid=MnwxMjA3fDB8MHxwaG90by1wYWdlfHx8fGVufDB8fHx8&amp;amp;auto=format&amp;amp;fit=crop&amp;amp;w=1351&amp;amp;q=80&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;5-use-supplements-for-immunity-boost-&#34;&gt;5. Use Supplements for immunity boost :&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We can use numerous supplements to immune our system that helps to fight against in COIVD-19 situation. We can use supplements as vitamins that contain in either liquid or powder form. There are below supplements we can use.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h6 id=&#34;-vitamin-c-it-may-help-to-reduce-infection-level&#34;&gt;* Vitamin C: It may help to reduce infection level.&lt;/h6&gt;
&lt;h6 id=&#34;-vitamin-d-it-helps-to-reduce-the-risk-of-cold-and-improve-the-immunity-system&#34;&gt;* Vitamin D: It helps to reduce the risk of cold and improve the immunity system.&lt;/h6&gt;
&lt;h6 id=&#34;-garlic----it-helps-to-reduce-viral-infection-and-care-for-a-common-cold&#34;&gt;* Garlic:    It helps to reduce viral infection and care for a common cold.&lt;/h6&gt;
&lt;h6 id=&#34;-zinc------it-also-helps-to-reduce-the-common-cold-when-it-took-within-24-hours-of-onset&#34;&gt;* Zinc:      It also helps to reduce the common cold when it took within 24 hours of onset.&lt;/h6&gt;
&lt;h6 id=&#34;-honey-----it-helps-to-fight-against-cough&#34;&gt;* Honey:     It helps to fight against cough.&lt;/h6&gt;
&lt;h6 id=&#34;-lemon-----intake-of-lemon-increases-the-digestive-system-and-reduces-the-level-of-viral-infection&#34;&gt;* Lemon:     Intake of lemon increases the digestive system and reduces the level of viral infection.&lt;/h6&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1611073061835-e77b1b16d3f3?ixlib=rb-1.2.1&amp;amp;ixid=MnwxMjA3fDB8MHxwaG90by1wYWdlfHx8fGVufDB8fHx8&amp;amp;auto=format&amp;amp;fit=crop&amp;amp;w=1351&amp;amp;q=80&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;mark&gt;Conclusion:&lt;/mark&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 8-hour quality sleep required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Eat healthy food on time that contains many minerals and vitamins.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avoid so much sugar, Instead of that use jaggery.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Drink lukewarm water.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Every day do Mediation, Yoga, and Exercise.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Increase intake of Tumeric, Garlic, Coriander, and Mint Leaves.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Use supplements for vitamins.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Use Lemon with lukewarm water everyday in the morning.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;as-we-are-fighting-against-the-covid-19-or-coronavirushttpswwwwhointhealth-topicscoronavirustabtab_1--pandemic-situation-so-we-must-follow-the-above-steps-to-cover-and-protect-ourselves&#34;&gt;As we are fighting against the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.who.int/health-topics/coronavirus#tab=tab_1&#34;&gt;Covid-19 or Coronavirus&lt;/a&gt;  pandemic situation so, we must follow the above steps to cover and protect ourselves.&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;stay-healthy-and-stay-fit&#34;&gt;Stay Healthy and Stay Fit.&lt;/h2&gt;

        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Why You Need to Do Yoga Daily ?</title>
      <link>https://darshkhatri.com/post/health/weight-lose/how-to-why-you-need-to-do-yoga-daily/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2021 16:29:40 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://darshkhatri.com/post/health/weight-lose/how-to-why-you-need-to-do-yoga-daily/</guid>
      <description>
        
          &lt;h2 id=&#34;yoga-came-from-the-sanskrit-word-yug-which-means-union&#34;&gt;YOGA came from the Sanskrit word &amp;quot;YUG&amp;quot; which means &amp;quot;UNION&amp;quot;.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are countless advantages of doing yoga every day.
Today I am discussing when, why, how you should do yoga.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In today&#39;s era, no one has abundant time to maintain health due to hectic work schedules and family responsibilities. There are several ways to take your body, mind, and soul to make it healthy but one of the best ways is &lt;code&gt;YOGA&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;1-what-is-yoga&#34;&gt;1. What is yoga?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There has no perfect definition of yoga. some people point it to be &lt;code&gt;Science&lt;/code&gt; or &lt;code&gt;Meditation&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In today&#39;s digital era people are mostly not have time to do exercise but yoga helps to reduce the stress of work and maintain balance peace of mind.
A number of research proven that by doing yoga you can solve the &#39;N&#39; number of diseases. Even you can be fit and look young and energetic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;2-how-we-can-do-yoga&#34;&gt;2. How we can do yoga?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are various methods of &#39;YOGA&#39; that you need to perform without disturbance. 
There are a few methods as I illustrated via picture.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://static6.depositphotos.com/1000419/605/v/600/depositphotos_6059748-stock-illustration-woman-practicing-yoga-25-poses.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;3-when-you-need-to-do-yoga&#34;&gt;3. When you need to do yoga?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Everyone is confused when we need to do yoga? what is the best time to do yoga?
As such, there has no fixed time to do yoga but there are numerous research proven that if someone does yoga in the morning so, it is beneficial for health, body, mind, and soul.
Because in the morning person have plenty of energy that&#39;s why it is fruitful to do yoga in the morning.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;4-advantages-of-yoga&#34;&gt;4. Advantages of yoga?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are countless benefits of doing yoga on a daily but I mention a few of them below.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;h6 id=&#34;improve-heart-health&#34;&gt;Improve heart health.&lt;/h6&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If someone doing yoga daily basis so it increases blood circulation and it can help lower blood, cholesterol, blood glucose level and maintain heart rate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;h6 id=&#34;relief-back-pain&#34;&gt;Relief back pain.&lt;/h6&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are several poses in yoga that relieve you from back pain and give you the energy to maintain your daily activity fastly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;h6 id=&#34;provide-you-more-energy-and-a-healthy-heart&#34;&gt;Provide you more energy and a healthy heart.&lt;/h6&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It provides you with more energy to achieve your daily goals as well as keep you mentally and physically active.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;h6 id=&#34;quality-sleep&#34;&gt;Quality sleep.&lt;/h6&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Doing yoga every day provides you to maintain a schedule and a relaxed mind that can help you for quality sleep.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;h6 id=&#34;protects-your-spine&#34;&gt;Protects your spine.&lt;/h6&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are different types of poses in yoga so, while performing that your body will be in good shape and make your bone stronger and protect your spine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;h6 id=&#34;improve-focus-power&#34;&gt;Improve focus power.&lt;/h6&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yoga has several poses that help with meditation. With the help of that meditation focus and decision power increase so, with less time achieve more things.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;note&#34;&gt;Note:&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If you are doing yoga the first time so, you need a trainer to understand how can perform yoga otherwise it&#39;s an effective wrong way.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;mark&gt;Conclusion:&lt;/mark&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Yoga has no specific definition.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;There are several poses that you can do yoga.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Yoga has numerous benefits.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You can do yoga either morning or evening but as per professional teacher morning yoga is more  effective.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best 2 Way to Loss Your Weight Tips</title>
      <link>https://darshkhatri.com/post/health/weight-lose/best-2-way-to-loss-your-weight-tips/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 18:05:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://darshkhatri.com/post/health/weight-lose/best-2-way-to-loss-your-weight-tips/</guid>
      <description>
        
          &lt;h4 id=&#34;heading&#34;&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;there-is-numerous-way-to-loss-bodyweight-but-out-of-all-of-those-i-will-let-you-know-about-the-most-effective-2-methods-of-losing-weight&#34;&gt;There is numerous way to loss bodyweight but out of all of those, I will let you know about the most effective 2 methods of losing weight.&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Weight is the most important factor for our body as well as our health, mind. we can face lots of issues due to overweight, but here I suggest you to some healthy tips to reduce your weight and maintain your balance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;1-eath-healthy-food&#34;&gt;1. Eath Healthy Food&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Healthy food is an extremely key point in our body and one of the very known quotes that I remember at this point is &amp;quot;You Are What You Eat&amp;quot;. We need to eat healthy food like vegetables, fruits as well as dried fruits such as almond, walnut, apricot, raisins, walnuts, etc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://images.pexels.com/photos/1295572/pexels-photo-1295572.jpeg?auto=compress&amp;amp;cs=tinysrgb&amp;amp;dpr=2&amp;amp;h=650&amp;amp;w=940&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Apart from the above, we can consume seeds like Chia seeds. We can inject that in several ways like: prepare ice cream or milk using seeds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://images.pexels.com/photos/5803171/pexels-photo-5803171.jpeg?auto=compress&amp;amp;cs=tinysrgb&amp;amp;dpr=2&amp;amp;h=650&amp;amp;w=940&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;how-can-we-forget-fruits-while-we-are-discussing-weight-loss-and-maintain-the-body&#34;&gt;How can we forget &amp;quot;Fruits&amp;quot; while we are discussing weight loss and maintain the body?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fruits are a natural source of gaining vitamins and nutrition for our body, so we can get plenty of energy to achieve our daily goals. We must eat fruits that contain ample water like watermelon, strawberries, peaches, orange, etc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Consumption of fruits is also effective for our skin plus the intestine and it also helps for increasing immunity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Remember that we need to eat so many colors at the time of lunch and breakfast, hence we can feel energetic in our fields.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://images.pexels.com/photos/1092730/pexels-photo-1092730.jpeg?cs=srgb&amp;amp;dl=pexels-jane-d-1092730.jpg&amp;amp;fm=jpg?auto=compress&amp;amp;cs=tinysrgb&amp;amp;dpr=2&amp;amp;h=650&amp;amp;w=940&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;2-natural-exerciseworkout&#34;&gt;2. Natural Exercise(WorkOut)&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;21-walking&#34;&gt;2.1 Walking&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is numerous exercise which you can do for reduce weight and belly fat. The primary exercise is &amp;quot;&lt;strong&gt;Walk&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;quot;. Every human needs to walk at least 30min per day, which helps to reduce weight and maintain the body, increased cardiovascular, decreased risk of heart stroke, or heart-related disease. &amp;quot;&lt;strong&gt;Walking&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;quot; helps to make a born stronger and burn calories. Apart from that below is more advantages of &amp;quot;&lt;strong&gt;30 minutes Walking&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;quot; every day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;advantage-of-30-minutes-walk&#34;&gt;Advantage of 30 minutes Walk.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Increase immunity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improve mental health&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creative Thinking&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It can help to control or lower blood sugar
&lt;img src=&#34;https://images.pexels.com/photos/1466852/pexels-photo-1466852.jpeg?cs=srgb&amp;amp;dl=pexels-yogendra-singh-1466852.jpg&amp;amp;fm=jpg?auto=compress&amp;amp;cs=tinysrgb&amp;amp;dpr=2&amp;amp;h=650&amp;amp;w=940&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;22-yoga&#34;&gt;2.2 Yoga&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Indian assistant foremost root for &amp;quot;&lt;strong&gt;exercise&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;quot; is &amp;quot;&lt;strong&gt;Yoga&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;quot; and now a day it is most popular to maintain a body and reduce weight. There are varipus pose in yoga that helps to reduce weight like : &amp;quot;&lt;strong&gt;Bhujangasana, Kumbhakasana, Naukasana, Ustrasana, Dhanurasana&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bhujangasana (Cobra pose)
&lt;img src=&#34;https://images.pexels.com/photos/4127315/pexels-photo-4127315.jpeg?cs=srgb&amp;amp;dl=pexels-yogendra-singh-1466852.jpg&amp;amp;fm=jpg?auto=compress&amp;amp;cs=tinysrgb&amp;amp;dpr=2&amp;amp;h=650&amp;amp;w=940&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kumbhakasana(The plank)
&lt;img src=&#34;https://images.pexels.com/photos/3823063/pexels-photo-3823063.jpeg?cs=srgb&amp;amp;dl=pexels-yogendra-singh-1466852.jpg&amp;amp;fm=jpg?auto=compress&amp;amp;cs=tinysrgb&amp;amp;dpr=2&amp;amp;h=650&amp;amp;w=940&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Naukasana(Boat pose)
&lt;img src=&#34;https://images.pexels.com/photos/4127327/pexels-photo-4127327.jpeg?cs=srgb&amp;amp;dl=pexels-yogendra-singh-1466852.jpg&amp;amp;fm=jpg?auto=compress&amp;amp;cs=tinysrgb&amp;amp;dpr=2&amp;amp;h=650&amp;amp;w=940&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ustrasana(Camel Pose)
&lt;img src=&#34;https://images.pexels.com/photos/4793286/pexels-photo-4793286.jpeg?cs=srgb&amp;amp;dl=pexels-yogendra-singh-1466852.jpg&amp;amp;fm=jpg?auto=compress&amp;amp;cs=tinysrgb&amp;amp;dpr=2&amp;amp;h=650&amp;amp;w=940&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dhanurasana(Bow pose)
&lt;img src=&#34;https://images.pexels.com/photos/3822366/pexels-photo-3822366.jpeg?auto=compress&amp;amp;cs=tinysrgb&amp;amp;dpr=2&amp;amp;h=650&amp;amp;w=940&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;strong&gt;Surya Namaskar&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;quot; is also best for maintaining the body, energy as well as fat loss.
It&#39;s a good cardio exercise and Its stances help in extending your stomach muscles making you shed pounds around the midsection so, approximately 10 minutes of &amp;quot;&lt;strong&gt;Surya Namaskar&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;quot; burning &amp;quot;&lt;strong&gt;139 calories&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;quot;. It is also helpful to bring down blood sugar levels.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Prefer timing for &amp;quot;&lt;strong&gt;Surya Namaskar&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;quot; is either in early(sunrise time) morning or late evening(sunset)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can follow the below way to do &amp;quot;&lt;strong&gt;Surya Namaskar&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;quot;.
&lt;img src=&#34;https://i.gifer.com/DYLV.gif?auto=compress&amp;amp;cs=tinysrgb&amp;amp;dpr=2&amp;amp;h=650&amp;amp;w=940&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;to-put-it-in-nutshell-the-above-two-methods-assist-you-to-help-improve-your-immune-system-if-you-follow-them-in-daily-routine-life-also-it-helps-to-reduce-weight&#34;&gt;To put it in nutshell, the above two methods assist you to help improve your immune system if you follow them in daily routine life also it helps to reduce weight.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;stay-healthy-and-stay-fit&#34;&gt;Stay Healthy and Stay Fit.&lt;/h2&gt;

        
      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
